(Let it go.)
=Revenge From A Wife=
=Episode 5=
Your Majesty.
I must still pay my respects
to the late Empress.
I'll take my leave.
Both are daughters of the Zhang family.
I thought by now
she'd learned some of Roujia's kindness
and good sense.
Instead, she's grown even more vicious.
Summon her!
Yes.
Your Majesty.
A victory report has arrived.
General Zhang
triumphed in the northern frontier
and captured three cities.
In his report, he says
his troops fought and bled,
and asks Your Majesty to reward them:
a thousand taels of gold
and a hundred qing of fertile land
to boost morale.
Consort Chen has quite the uncle.
Not only can he win battles,
he even
decides what rewards and favors
I should bestow.
Next time,
he'll be asking for my imperial seal.
Your Majesty!
I'm only joking.
I still need his troops
to hold the northern frontier.
Make sure the maid's family
is properly compensated.
Pick out a few suitable gifts
and send them to Concubine Yu.
She served the late Empress, after all.
Don't let her feel slighted.
Yes.
Father.
Come here.
What's that in your hand?
The lady at the herbal medicine stall
outside the cottage gave it to me.
It smells just like the calming incense
Mother burned when I was little.
It has a faint herbal scent.
It's quite soothing.
Li Dehai.
Yes?
Come for a walk with me.
Yes.
Your Majesty.
(Medicine)
Looks like I'm too late.
Your Majesty.
Shall I
send someone to find her?
Never mind.
You lured him here.
Why leave now?
If he gets what he wants too easily,
he won't appreciate it.
But if you won't even see him,
what if he leaves
and never comes back?
This scent
came from the woman Xiao Che loves.
Once he smells it,
he won't forget it.
If he can't forget it,
he'll come back.
Your Majesty.
You look
much better today
than you have lately.
I did sleep
quite well last night.
Oh!
The stall owner
is burning herbs this early.
I'm going out for a walk.
Yes, Your Majesty.
♪Sunset fades beyond the lonely city♪
♪Dusk snow paints the green hills♪
♪A lone rider storms the old pass♪
♪Drunk, I gaze by lamplight♪
♪Old friends have all drifted away♪
♪My broken sword rusts, as do I♪
♪Jackdaws cry into the night♪
♪Half a banner snaps in the wind♪
♪In dreams, I return to the camps♪
♪Moonlight chills my armor♪
♪Life is a dream through many winters♪
♪I gaze beyond the edge of the world♪
♪Parting sorrow spills across the moon♪
♪The moon and wind mean nothing now♪
♪History turns to ash before ink dries♪
♪Who plays the zither
and sighs at the pavilion?♪
♪The past has faded away♪